[
  {
    "question": "メプチンミニ",
    "correct": "プロカテロール",
    "choices": [
      "クレンブテロール",
      "プロカテロール",
      "ツロブテロール",
      "フェノテロール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ピーゼットシ",
    "correct": "ペルフェナジンマレイン",
    "choices": [
      "ペルフェナジンマレイン",
      "ブロナンセリン",
      "ナテグリニド",
      "フルスルチアミン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "パーキネス",
    "correct": "トリヘキシフェニジル",
    "choices": [
      "エルロチニブ",
      "トリヘキシフェニジル",
      "ベルベリン・ゲンノショウコエキス",
      "ブロムフェナク"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ベオーバ",
    "correct": "ビベグロン",
    "choices": [
      "ファモチジン",
      "トロンビン",
      "ビベグロン",
      "ベルベリン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "サワシリン",
    "correct": "アモキシシリン",
    "choices": [
      "デュロキセチン",
      "リマプロストアルファデクス",
      "アモキシシリン",
      "マグネシウム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ソリタ",
    "correct": "カリウムマグネシウム",
    "choices": [
      "カリウムマグネシウム",
      "エソメプラゾールマグネシウム",
      "アルミニウムゲル・マグネシウム",
      "マグネシウム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "メジコン",
    "correct": "デキストロメトルファンクレゾールスルホンカリウム",
    "choices": [
      "エキセメスタン",
      "バルプロ",
      "デキストロメトルファンクレゾールスルホンカリウム",
      "アトルバスタチンカルシウム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "エンレスト",
    "correct": "サクビトリルバルサルタン",
    "choices": [
      "アジルサルタン",
      "サクビトリルバルサルタン",
      "ロサルタン",
      "バルサルタン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ジャディアンス",
    "correct": "エンパグリフロジン",
    "choices": [
      "アズレン",
      "バルプロ",
      "ガラクトシダーゼアスペルギルス",
      "エンパグリフロジン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "リオベル",
    "correct": "アログリプチンピオグリタゾン",
    "choices": [
      "アログリプチンピオグリタゾン",
      "カリジノゲナーゼ",
      "ジオクチルソジウムスルホサクシネート・カサンスラノール",
      "ピオグリタゾン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "テネリア",
    "correct": "テネリグリプチン",
    "choices": [
      "ケトプロフェン",
      "テネリグリプチン",
      "ブデソニド・ホルモテロール",
      "ピリドキシン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "タケルダ",
    "correct": "アスピリンランソプラゾール",
    "choices": [
      "アスピリンランソプラゾール",
      "オメプラゾール",
      "アリピプラゾール",
      "ランソプラゾール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ハルシオン",
    "correct": "トリアゾラム",
    "choices": [
      "レパグリニド",
      "エトドラク",
      "トリアゾラム",
      "ホリナートカルシウム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "レキソタン",
    "correct": "ブロマゼパム",
    "choices": [
      "ペルゴリドメシル",
      "フルスルチアミン",
      "イプリフラボン",
      "ブロマゼパム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "イクスタンジ",
    "correct": "エンザルタミド",
    "choices": [
      "ビカルタミド",
      "フルタミド",
      "フルニトラゼパム",
      "エンザルタミド"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "サムチレール",
    "correct": "アトバコン",
    "choices": [
      "レパグリニド",
      "ラタノプロスト・チモロール",
      "デスモプレシン",
      "アトバコン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "バフセオ",
    "correct": "バダデュスタット",
    "choices": [
      "カンデサルタンシレキセチル・ヒドロクロロチアジド",
      "フェブキソスタット",
      "バダデュスタット",
      "エパルレスタット"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ジレニア",
    "correct": "フィンゴリモド",
    "choices": [
      "オウヒエキス",
      "ペルゴリドメシル",
      "フィンゴリモド",
      "プロプラノロール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "タリージェ",
    "correct": "ミロガバリンベシル",
    "choices": [
      "ミロガバリンベシル",
      "カンデサルタンシレキセチル・アムロジピンベシル",
      "テルミサルタン・アムロジピンベシル",
      "バルサルタン・アムロジピンベシル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ビオフェルミン",
    "correct": "ラクトミン",
    "choices": [
      "ヘパリン",
      "イブプロフェン",
      "ラクトミン",
      "リルゾール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ネシーナ",
    "correct": "アログリプチン",
    "choices": [
      "アダパレン",
      "レゾルシン",
      "アログリプチン",
      "ピコスルファート"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "トラゼンタ",
    "correct": "リナグリプチン",
    "choices": [
      "リナグリプチン",
      "ナフトピジル",
      "アルジオキサ",
      "リスペリドン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "デエビゴ",
    "correct": "レンボレキサント",
    "choices": [
      "レンボレキサント",
      "ビペリデン",
      "クアゼパム",
      "フェノフィブラート"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "テノーミン",
    "correct": "アテノロール",
    "choices": [
      "アロチノロール",
      "レボブノロール",
      "アテノロール",
      "プロプラノロール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "エフィエント",
    "correct": "プラスグレル",
    "choices": [
      "フルコナゾール",
      "ゾニサミド",
      "プラスグレル",
      "ニカルジピン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アコファイド",
    "correct": "アコチアミド",
    "choices": [
      "アコチアミド",
      "ツロブテロール",
      "オオウメガサソウエキス・ハコヤナギエキス",
      "グリベンクラミド"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "レキサルティ",
    "correct": "ブレクスピプラゾール",
    "choices": [
      "オメプラゾール",
      "ブレクスピプラゾール",
      "ランソプラゾール",
      "アリピプラゾール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ダーブロック",
    "correct": "ダプロデュスタット",
    "choices": [
      "エパルレスタット",
      "エペリゾン",
      "ダプロデュスタット",
      "フェブキソスタット"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ゾコーバ",
    "correct": "エンシトレルビルフマル",
    "choices": [
      "ベタメタゾンエステル",
      "エンシトレルビルフマル",
      "ナフトピジル",
      "クアゼパム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ラスビック",
    "correct": "ラスクフロキサシン",
    "choices": [
      "レボフロキサシン",
      "ラスクフロキサシン",
      "シプロフロキサシン",
      "シタフロキサシン"
    ]
  }
]